== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
(Leonard:)Did you at least have
a good flight down there?
(Sheldon:)It was fine.
(Sheldon:)Other than the weird-tasting
juice Amy gave me.
(Sheldon:)I slept the whole way.
(Penny:)So, what happened in Texas
that was so bad?
(Leonard:)And before our next
drive to Comic-Con,
(Leonard:)I need the name of that juice.
(Sheldon:)Well, we were on our way
to my mother's house...
(Sheldon:)How did we get in the car?
Hold on.
How did you get him
in the car?
(Amy:)I rented one of those carts,
(Amy:)pushed him toward the open
door and just let inertia
(Amy:)take care of the rest.
(Amy:)So, while we're at
your mother's house,
(Amy:)it might be a good time to tell
her that we're living together.
(Sheldon:)Do we have to?
(Sheldon:)I really don't want
to hear the religious lecture.
(Amy:)Maybe there won't be one.
(Sheldon:)There's always one.